John said, how do you build case studies?
You ask your clients for revenue?
No, we don't talk about revenue.
We talk about the scope of work that we're contracted to do.
If it's increasing traffic, if we have lead data
and leads are increasing, we'll do that.
You know, whatever The most valuable piece of data
that we can pull from is we'll use that revenue data.
Like we're e-commerce would be good if you're,
if you're doing that, you know, for
e-commerce, 'cause you definitely have access to that data.
But like we don't get revenue data
'cause legal variant,
it could be 5,000, it could be 5 million.
They don't tell us that. There's
also privacy issues with that.
But if you look at the case studies on weber.org, if you go
to weber.org and then go to results, you'll see,
I think we have four up there now.
And I'm starting to put together more
and more, I'm trying to get more
for our Facebook ads practice.
It's just, they're kind of a pain to write and build.
Although CHATT does a really good job with 'em.
I think most of us are written by CHATT now,
but we'll just extract whatever we have access to.
Sometimes it's just traffic information and that's fine.
You know, it's better than nothing. Andre said,
how do you ensure you're speaking
to the decision maker or not?
And if not, do you reschedule?
That's a very good question, Andre.
So you wanna make sure you ask that
during the discovery process.
So one of the questions that was in there
that I didn't actually say aloud was, Hey,
when we do the analysis,
how does Thursday at two look awesome?
Is there anybody else that needs to be there?
And if they're like, no. And it's like, okay,
so you can ask this if you're having an issue with this.
And Andrea, so you can ask the question.
So are you, so I can expect a decision from you
after we go through this, right?
You can just ask them directly.
You don't have to say like, again,
wording is very important here
because we don't want to, we don't want to belittle people
or, uh, be like, are you the decision maker?
It's a little bit condescending if you're like,
are you the decision maker of the business?
It's like, yeah, I'm the business owner.
Or it's like, no, I'm just, I'm not, you know?
And so like, just making sure
that we're using the right language
of is there anybody else that needs to be there?
Who else should I invite to the call? You know?
And then if they're like, no, nobody,
and you should know this too, Andres.
'cause you, you should do a little bit
of research on the person,
you know, you can check them out on LinkedIn.
If it's like a, if it's like a internal social media man,
we'll get that sometimes too, like intake people,
like salespeople or like assistants will sometimes book
with us and they'll go through the discovery call
and I'm like, I'm not gonna, I don't say this,
but I'm like, I'm not gonna do the analysis for you.
Like, I'll, I'll, I'll say like, you know, can, like,
should instead of like, can we,
it's like should we invite the attorney to the, the call?
You know? And if they're like, no, I'll handle it,
then I'm like, so you're prepared to make, are you gonna be
prepared to make the decision on this?
You know, there's a lot of money involved.
I just wanna make sure that you're the, you're the person
that I should talk to about the decision for this.
Right? So language is important.
We just wanna make sure that we're not being
condescending as we do that.
'cause it can be like said, people sometimes ask
for references, which is annoying.
I hammer testimonials,
but I don't like the idea
of giving out other client phone numbers.
Have you dealt with anything like that?
How do you deal with it? How to avoid it? Yeah.
We're going through a phase right now where,
because we're, we're being used
as like a subcontractor, white label partner.
Not even a full white label partner.
Like they're, they're using our agency name,
but they're, it's their
clients that they're giving us the work to.
And then they tackle a little bit on top.
And because we are kind of an unknown for their clients,
they're a lot are asking for references
and we give them two, we, we have like three that we use.
I don't even know if they honestly
hit 'em up every time. Michael.
Like, I don't think that they do,
but we just give them out
because it's kind of like, man f it, you know what I mean?
Like, we're, we're, you're not gonna get the account if they
ask for it and you're like, no,
then you're just not gonna get the account.
So, you know, like you gotta have,
you sh you gotta have one at least on deck
that you can, that you can call on.
And if they, if you have to give it out a lot, you know,
you just make sure to incentivize that that client,
you know, to be like, Hey look at,
you've been a great reference for us.
I'm gonna, we're gonna discount
or I'm gonna send you something for that.
It's annoying though dude. It's annoying.
So Sean said, how many discovery calls
do you average a week?
Depends. Do some weeks. Zero some weeks. 10.
You know, average is not the right way to, I mean,
I guess like average over time.
But like, you know, we crush lead generation.
We just fricking crush it. It's what we do.
We're also getting a lot of leads referred to us by,
by this other agency right now, which is,
which is a blessing.
Alright. Steven said, what are some good numbers
to hit X amount of discovery calls a month
or week in close x?
I know that can vary, but a ballpark number.
It's, it's less, it's, it's a fair question Steven,
but it's kinda like the one from Sean where it's like,
I don't know, like discovery calls are kind of, kind
of like, I just care about signed deals.
Like I would, I I,
I'm not optimizing against discovery calls,
I'm opting against signed clients and I
like to try and sign four a month.
Like one per week is usually what my goal is.
Some months we do less than that.
Some months we do more than that.
So it's really more you have to start with
how many clients you want per month
and then you can kind of back out
how many discovery calls you need for that.
But if you start with discovery calls, it's kind of,
it's almost like a vanity metric
because you know you might close 30%
of discovery calls, right?
So you wanna start with the number,
like I have a client goal per month,
which is based on my growth goals
of the year, if that makes sense.
Like if I could sign for four clients a month,
we're doing damage in some months it's
more, some months it's way less.
You know, last month was a really slow month.
We only signed I think one
client, you know, it's very up and down.
This business time of year matters.
Your ad campaigns matter.
Whatever way the wind is blowing matters.
There's a lot of stuff that goes into it that are
outside of our control sometimes.
So close rate too, Steven, again,
it depends a lot on lead quality.
Like if you're running a lot of close rate
to me depends on two things.
Number one, it's lead quality
and source number two, it's gonna be your offer.
So if you're, if you're getting referrals,
like we're getting a lot of referrals right now from this
other agency, uh, and they're, we're closing about,
it's a little bit complicated 'cause we're pitching us
another agency but like these are closing at like 50 to 60%,
which is great, you know,
from introduction to close, which is good.
Referrals are always gonna close to highest,
but they don't scale that well because
you don't have control over it.
For our paid ads, our SEO was closing at like 10
to 20%, like really low.
But SEO deals are kind of hard
to close 'cause the offer stinks.
You know, SEO is just like kind of a, a bad offer
because it's not for everyone.
You can't really forecast results.
But when we started pivoting to to Facebook ads as our offer
and I could tell them very specifically what they can expect
to pay per signed case.
Our close rate is like, you know, 40 to 50% from ads.
You know, and that's really good.
Now the downside to, that's a much higher churn, right?
So it kind of evens out in the backend.
But you know, it really depends,
like your close rate really depends on
what the lead source is and,
and uh, you know what your offer is.
If you just kinda got like a standard SEO offer
to commodity at this point, you know,
we're only pitching SEO's referral deals
'cause they do pay traffic for themselves.
But that's under like a larger umbrella of, you know, a lot
of these referrals are doing like billboards and like radio
and PPC ads.
SEO is kind of like the final piece that, you know,
it just fits into their overall marketing ecosystem.
So they close pretty well. Michael said maybe I just build
the referral, go to guys
and give a discount after giving the results.
Yeah, definitely. Like you, you should really aim
to have at least one and you should definitely tell them
ahead of time that hey, I'm gonna be sending some,
some prospects your way.
You know, is that okay? You gotta ask 'em first.
If you don't, it can cut. Like it
can, it can backfire on you.
You know, you then be like, I don't know who,
who this guy Michael is I'm talking about.
So just make sure you rent it by
and then yeah, you can definitely incentivize them.
You know, you don't wanna like bribe them,
but you know, if they give a good referral, like what we did
with one of our clients is, is uh, you know, we,
we asked them if we could give
them and he said, yeah, that's fine.
He got contacted and we closed the deal
and the deal was actually, yeah, like, you know, one
of the reasons why we went with you is
because that attorney gave you like a glowing response.
So we sent him like a gift
and you know, we told him that we're like, you know,
if if he's willing to serve as a referral
for us too in the future, then you know, we're happy
to give him a discount,
a 500 a month discount, which is well worth it.
So you definitely wanna take care of him.
Gabriel said once you have a proposal
analysis review call set, what do you think
of sending a five to 10 minute loom, 24 hours ahead
of the call with the analysis
and proposal setting their expectations accordingly?
I don't love that Gabriel. I mean I don't hate it.
I guess I don't love it because I don't like
to give them any information ahead of the call
that it's gonna potentially,
that can be interpreted without me there, right?
Again, working through this referral partner,
they keep asking me for these analysis and proposals
and they're sending to them the prospect without,
without having a call with me.
And I'm like, yo, this is like, I'm not doing this anymore
because you get, you, you get something
that's 40 slides long, it's like Chinese to you
and then you just see the price tag in it
and you're like, dad, no I'm, I'm good.
You know, like you have to be able to walk them through it.
So I think looms are very impactful
but it's more for like, I would do it more
for like the scope of work where it doesn't really need it.
Like a loom should be used either.
It's like a reengagement tool to be like, hey,
we spoke six months ago, you ghost dummy,
that's fine, wink, wink.
But whoever's managing SEO is really dropping the ball.
Look at your traffic, you know, like I'm around, let's talk.
It's like, it's a very personal kind
of like reengagement tool
or as an explainer tool for in use in,
in lieu of a call, right?
So like I don't always love to get on a call with somebody
who tells me yes and walk them through the details
of the scope of work 'cause it's very boring.
So I'll send them a loom walking them through it
and then instruct them on next steps.
And you wanna make sure to keep them
to less than five minutes Gabriel.
'cause like you send a like a 10, 15, 20 minute loon.
They're not watching that dude. I don't, when people send it
to me, I come, I'm like, dude, come on man.
Like this is, this is a little bit heavy, you know?
So you wanna make sure that you're using 'em accordingly.
Sean said, are you noticing
that the agency business is being affected
by any economic conditions?
My death clients are asking reduce their
services a lot last three months.
No. At all. No, I'm not seeing that at all.
That to me is, I don't know, maybe lawyers are different.
Maybe like people always need lawyers
but like people always need the dentist too.
I mean like maybe people are cutting back due
to inconsistency Sean, but like to me, part of my French,
it just sounds like they're puckering their butts
because they're scared and they're not getting the results
or the expectations that they expect.
And that's not a dig at you that's just like,
like economic dude.
This is America. Like people are always be money, always.
You know, like I know that like we're supposed
to be in recessions and all this like every eight,
10 years, whatever it is in economic cycles.
I have not seen that one bit.
I've been doing this for 15 years.
I have been
through I guess not too many recessions like COVID, right?
I guess COVID was like one,
but like COVID didn't affect the economy at all, man.
People were started spending more
and now post COVID, it's like,
I don't wanna say this country's like recession proof,
but like we just spend so much money on the internet now.
Like our economy has moved online, you know, you know,
people aren't like walking down the street getting yellow
pages to find a dentist anymore.
You know, like they're doing it through the internet.
So unless people are all of a sudden being like, yeah,
I'm just gonna let my teeth rot out of my face, you know,
then I think they're, they're just, they're puckering
and it just sounds like they're kind of cheap, you know,
which happens, you know.
But with our lawyer clients, not at all man.
People are trying to spend more money because the way
that they see it is that people always need lawyers
for whatever, you know, model that they're in.
So, you know, I did work, I was working
with a consulting client in the cannabis space that
that cut me this past year because their revenue was down.
But like it's also 'cause of the company.
Like they kind of overextended and stuff like that.
So no, I haven't seen any of that shown.
I don't know if anyone else in
here you can raise your hands.
There's only other people in here that can comment on that.
But I have not seen that.
Yeah, so Michael said, got someone who's gonna gimme a lot
of referrals, old friends shutting down her marketing
company, same process, discovery proposal, et cetera.
It just depends on the relationship
with the refer the person, the agency that's referring
to us is actually fine with us using our name and logo
because also they kind of have to,
because I'm very visible on the internet, so you know,
assuming people do any Googling on me, they're gonna see
that I own an agency.
But clients are fine with it, they don't care.
It's really just up to the referring partner.
Like some referring partners are like, no, I want you
to do this under my brand.
You know, I do that. I'm using a, a kid
who does generates reviews
and um, I'm white labeling it, I'm, it's not white label.
I'm subcontracting and I'm like, no,
like you're doing this under our brand.
You know, I'm gonna push a lot of,
but that's just, that's just for these particular ones.
'cause I want the client reviews are such a big part
of like local SEO that I want them to think
that we're doing it in a sense.
So yeah. And then also Sean Michael said
has not seen in home services.
That's one that I hear a lot. I dunno if he's in here now,
Steven with the home countertops.
I think he asked about that inner circle too, like,
like home services is another one too where it's like,
you know, home remodelers like, oh, like the economy's down.
So maybe Sean, the dentists are hurting
because you know, actual necessities, you know,
we're cutting back on so we can spend more stuff on
vanity stuff that we don't need.
Yeah, like home remodelers.
I used, I mean all the time dude, I like,
oh like there's a supply chain shortage.
So like it costs more
and people like are people still paying?
Yeah, they're still paying. Okay, so what's the issue then?
It's just that they don't want to pay.
They're just scared, you know, and that's fine.
I mean we're all, I think it's something we can all
empathize with as business owners that like,
if you've ever spent, I mean
how many people here have have an agency or marketing
or advertising expenses?
Probably not many, you know?
So like there's a certain level of empathy that we have
to have because we're asking them
to do something that we don't do.
You know? I mean I do it so I understand,
but like I didn't always do it.
So, you know, it can be frustrating.
But now I have a level of empathy to be like, I get it,
dude, spending 25 grand a month is a lot.
You know, or even five grand, you know, for some businesses.
And if they don't feel like their expectations are being
met, and again, Sean, this isn't to dig on you at all.
I know you do a great job, but it's really, that
to me is less about, they're just blaming that
because maybe they don't wanna have a hard conversation
with you and they're just puckering up.
Like we have clients all the time that wanna reduce spend
or they don't blame it on the economy though.
But it's hard for us as agencies sometimes
because it's frustrating
because it's like, yo, you gotta spend money, make money.
But, you know, that's why I always encourage us
to do our own marketing because it, it not only raises your,
I mean that makes you better at what we do and builds it,
but it's a source of credibility and trust for prospects.
'cause like you're asking them to do something
that you're doing for yourself.
You know, I guarantee you there's probably not one person in
here who's investing in SEO for their own agency.
How many people are spending money every month on SEO
content development link building?
The point is, is that, uh, you know, like we're asking them
to do stuff a lot of times that,
that we ask the couplers kids have no shoes, right?
And that I'm not digging at you guys, obviously I love all
of you, but you know, it's just something
to keep in mind if like, if you, it it's something
that I'm sure pops into their mind sometimes if they're
like, alright, you're asking, you're quoting
me $4,000 a month.
Like, can I see what you're doing for yours?
And you're like, uh, you know, I've been there.
Before I get on said, do you think doing organic social
media for your own agency is the highest ROI
daily post high quality?
Yeah, I do. I don't think it's the highest ROI,
but I think it's the best thing that you can do
because that then you have assets
that you can use for advertising.
And I also just think that, I mean,
I've seen this just a quick personal note,
like my YouTube channels have died
long form video is not what it used to be.
I think because YouTube has gotten a lot more crowded
and it's gotten a lot more like entertainment based.
Like, I do like deep educational content
and I don't think as many people wanna sit
and watch like a 15, 30 minute video as much as they used
to, to get like, information
that's more readily available now.
You know, I see the marketing content
that does really well now is a little bit more like cuts
and flashes and like engagement base and like,
and I'm gonna update like, duh Scott.
Like I, I just don't, I, I'm not very good at that type
of content, you know, but short form video, you know,
like a minute or less reels, shorts, TikTok, like, yeah,
that to me is where a lot of the market has gone.
We, so we focus a lot there.
But then that also gives us assets that we can advertise,
which obviously is what drives a lot of our business.